<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_1283047703/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_1283047703/</guid>
      <description>Today, we see a mixed reaction among conservative-leaning scientists following the Trump administration’s swift changes in federal health and science agencies, and we hear one idea on how Canada could respond to the new 25% tariffs. advertisement These updates and more are reflected in the latest update of STAT’s Obesity Drug Tracker, which gives a comprehensive look at the status and approaches that dozens of drug companies are taking to help people lose weight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_1635987260/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_1635987260/</guid>
      <description>This story first appeared in Adam’s Biotech Scorecard, a subscriber-only newsletter. Log in Monthly $39 Totals $468 per year Totals $468 per year Starter $30 for 3 months, then $399/year Then $399/year Annual $399 Save 15% Save 15% 11+ Users Custom Savings start at 25%! 2-10 Users $300 Annually per user $300 Annually per user To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_1642347710/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_1642347710/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_2600563399/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_2600563399/</guid>
      <description>advertisement The agreement comes less than a year since Robert Michael took over as CEO of AbbVie and as the company looks for its next top-selling drugs following the loss of patent protection for its mega blockbuster autoimmune treatment Humira. In a statement, Michael said that the Gubra partnership offers “a compelling opportunity based on the potential to address patient needs while also fostering long-term growth for our company.” STAT+ Exclusive Story Already have an account?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3301497820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3301497820/</guid>
      <description>advertisement Bhattacharya also said he is “convinced” vaccines don’t cause autism, but won’t rule out more studies on the issue, even as Republican Sen. Bill Cassidy countered him, arguing that producing more studies is “plowing over ground that has been plowed over.” If confirmed, Bhattacharya would work under HHS Secretary RFK Jr., who has refused to say that vaccines don’t cause autism. Novo Nordisk said yesterday that it will start selling its obesity drug Wegovy directly to patients at a reduced price, following a similar move from Eli Lilly, though Novo’s offering is broader.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3516347308/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3516347308/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON — Marty Makary took the opportunity to play the Make America Healthy Again movement’s greatest hits at his Senate confirmation hearing Thursday for Food and Drug Administration commissioner. Log in Monthly $39 Totals $468 per year Totals $468 per year Starter $30 for 3 months, then $399/year Then $399/year Annual $399 Save 15% Save 15% 11+ Users Custom Savings start at 25%! 2-10 Users $300 Annually per user $300 Annually per user To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3668511496/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3668511496/</guid>
      <description>An experimental medicine from Protagonist Therapeutics stabilized red blood cells and improved symptoms in patients with a rare blood cancer — achieving the efficacy goals of a Phase 3 study. The companies are developing the drug as a new treatment for polycythemia vera, a type of blood cancer that causes the overproduction of red blood cells. Log in Monthly $39 Totals $468 per year Totals $468 per year Starter $30 for 3 months, then $399/year Then $399/year Annual $399 Save 15% Save 15% 11+ Users Custom Savings start at 25%!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3791158596/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_3791158596/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_4125642389/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_4125642389/</guid>
      <description>Today, we talk about the likely confirmation of FDA nominee Marty Makary, go in-depth on NIH nominee Jay Bhattacharya, and see how much 23andMe CEO Anne Wojcicki is willing to pay for her own company. advertisement Marty Makary, President Trump’s nominee for FDA commissioner, has pledged to divest stock holdings and resign from advisory roles in various health tech, pharmaceutical, and medical device companies if confirmed, STAT’s Lizzy Lawrence reports. advertisement The findings suggested the fees led to agency bias and raise questions about whether coverage of many of the medicines should be paid for by the different government agencies, the study author told STAT’s Ed Silverman.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_821558500/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_821558500/</guid>
      <description>advertisement “We don’t want to be in a situation where we’re in a data-free zone and having to make educated guesses when it involves the health of so many people,” said Luciana Borio, former director for medical and biodefense preparedness policy at the National Security Council. From STAT’s Helen Branswell: There have been concerns that production and delivery of next winter’s flu shots might be delayed, given the unexplained cancellation of a meeting of the FDA’s vaccines advisory committee, which had initially been scheduled for mid-March.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_844367382/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_844367382/</guid>
      <description>Jazz Pharmaceuticals said Wednesday it would spend nearly $1 billion to buy Chimerix and its experimental pill for a devastating brain tumor that primarily affects children and young adults. Log in Monthly $39 Totals $468 per year Totals $468 per year Starter $30 for 3 months, then $399/year Then $399/year Annual $399 Save 15% Save 15% 11+ Users Custom Savings start at 25%! 2-10 Users $300 Annually per user $300 Annually per user To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_995064827/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhanhuizhang.github.io/posts/20250307_995064827/</guid>
      <description>“We’ve been making headway on subleases, but we still have a lot of lab space available that we’d love to get you into.” STAT+ Exclusive Story Already have an account? Log in Monthly $39 Totals $468 per year Totals $468 per year Starter $30 for 3 months, then $399/year Then $399/year Annual $399 Save 15% Save 15% 11+ Users Custom Savings start at 25%! 2-10 Users $300 Annually per user $300 Annually per user To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
